Ever since it happened, life has been great,
friend.  Watching him play, it feels like I am
watching my own childhood.  And what
are its demands?  Hey, what
demands already?  Right now, Papa, I just want to drink milk,
eat chocolate and watch these cartoons.  This is what keeps happening.
Papa, I need one lakh rupees.  College fees have to be paid.   It doesn't take
long for children and their needs to grow.
Therefore, prepare for their future from today.
Smart Kit Assur vs ICICI
Prudential Signature Assur lets your
investment grow with your children
and offers life cover and premium
waiver along with family income benefits,
meaning your policy will continue to be in force no matter what happens to you.
ICICI Pro's Smart Kit
Assure Plan tomorrow and prepare today.  Hmm.